smeclub.net 2008-05-17

# SMECLUB Support

## SMECommunity » Using the website  

## Privacy Statement

Venture Vanguard Limited, publisher of smeclub.net, and its affiliates (hereafter referred to collectively as "VENTURE VANGUARD") are committed to maintaining the privacy of personal information that you provide to us when using smeclub.net. This Privacy Policy describes how we treat personal information received about you when you visit smeclub.net. 

**Your Privacy Is Serious Business To Us!**

The privacy of our visitors and members is very important to us. Since we do gather information about you, we provide this privacy statement to enable you understand the terms and conditions associated with the collection of this data, as well as how we use it and how you can correct or change it. In addition, we make to you the following pledge: 

**SMEclub Privacy Pledge**

The information we collect about your business will be used for purposes of site research and development in an effort to better serve your needs. 

We will never contact you without your permission, and we will immediately terminate any communications with you upon your request. 

**Links to Other Web Sites**

smeclub.net features content from VENTURE VANGUARD as well as a collection of services that are offered by third parties, including a database of businesses for sale, a business plan builder tool and other services. In order to use these third-party services you will be directed to pages on their web sites, which may or may not be co-branded with our logo. Remember that any information that you provide on any third party pages is being provided directly to the third-party service provider and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. We recommend that you review the privacy policy at each third-party Web site to determine how that site protects your privacy. 

**Information We Collect**

 **Web Site Usage Information** : We automatically collect IP addresses and Web site usage information from you when you visit our Web site. This information helps us evaluate how our visitors use and navigate our Web site on an aggregate basis, including the number and frequency of visitors to each Web page, and the length of their visits. 

**General** : When you use some of the siteâ€™s special features, such as registering for e-mail alerts, requesting information, participating in discussion groups, and at other times, we will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, phone number, address, e-mail address and similar information. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. 

**Surveys** : We may conduct occasional online surveys. For example, when you are within our Web site, you may see a pop-up window offering you the optional opportunity of participating in a survey. These surveys are entirely voluntary and you may easily decline to participate. 

**How We Use Information Collected**

 **We may use information in the following ways:**

  * For the purposes for which you specifically provided the information, for example, to review and post your contributions to discussion groups and to process and forward to franchisers your franchiser information requests. 

  * To send you e-mail notifications about our new or existing products and services, special offers, or to otherwise contact you. 

  * To allow us to personalize the content and advertising that you and others see based on personal characteristics or preferences. 

  * To enhance existing features or develop new features, products and services. 

  * To provide advertisers and other third parties with aggregate information about our user base and usage patterns. 

  * We may combine the information that we collect from you on this Web site with information that you provide to us in connection with your use of our other products, services and Web sites.

We use third parties, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to deliver ads to you on our behalf. We may also use third-party service providers to contact you on our behalf, or facilitate some aspects of our Web site services, or fulfill your purchase requests. These third-party ad servers and service providers may be supplied with or have access to your personally identifiable information solely for the purpose of providing these services to us or on our behalf. 

These third-party ad servers may also collect and use non-personally identifiable information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to present advertisements that may be of interest to you. 

Except as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personally identifiable information outside of VENTURE VANGUARD unless you "opt in" to having your personally identifiable information shared with a company that is not affiliated with us. 

When you ask for information about Franchisers in the Franchiser Section of our site, we will forward your contact information to the Franchisers that you have selected. 

We may disclose and use personally identifiable information in special circumstances where it is necessary to enforce our Terms of Use (for example, when necessary to protect our intellectual property rights) or when we, in our sole discretion, believe it is necessary or appropriate, in connection with a sale or transfer of some or all of our assets in the Web site. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires us to do so. 

**Your Ability to Choose**

You may sign up for e-mail alerts by providing us with your name and e-mail address. You may unsubscribe from these alerts by returning to the e-mail alerts page on the site and following the instructions for unsubscribing. We will provide a link to this page at the bottom of every e-mail we send to you. 

**Cookies**

We use cookies to allow you to move quickly through our site, to recognize repeat visitors and to allow you to take advantage of some of our siteâ€™s special features. A cookie is a string of information that is sent by a Web site and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. Cookies are small files (just a few hundred bytes) and wonâ€™t pose any significant disk-space concerns. 

During your sessions here, you also will receive cookies from our third-party service providers or third party network advertisers. The network advertisers may use their own cookies in order to serve ads on our Web sites, ensuring that you wonâ€™t see the same ads over and over again. 

**Smeclub.net Ads**

When you view an ad for smeclub.net on other sites, our third party advertising company may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. smeclub.net and its advertising company may also use invisible images (often referred to as pixel tags, clear GIFs or web beacons) to note which smeclub.net pages you visit after viewing our ads. The information that is collected through the use of these images is not personally identifiable and is used only to track responses to our advertising efforts. 

**Security**

The personally identifiable information we collect about you is stored in limited access servers. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personally identifiable information. 

**Reporting Unsolicited E-mail**

Despite our concerted efforts to prevent unsolicited (spam) e-mail relayed through The SME Club servers, unsolicited e-mail may sometimes get through. The SME Club NEVER sends unsolicited or spam e-mail. We view spam as a serious violation of privacy and a misuse of the Internet in general. If you receive an unsolicited e-mail with a domain of The SME Club, please send it immediately to [support@smeclub.net](mailto:support@smeclub.net). Upon receipt of the email, we will do our utmost to track down the offender and take any actions necessary to stop spam messages. 

**Review and Correction**

You may update or delete the personally identifiable information that you have provided to us by contacting us at [support@smeclub.net](mailto:support@smeclub.net) . 

**Policy Modifications**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically. 

**Comments and Questions**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns about our Privacy Policy, you may contact us by e-mail at support[@smeclub.net](mailto:support@smeclub.net)

Last update: 2007-10-04 17:31  
Author: Webmaster

Print this record  
Send to a friend  
Show this as PDF file  
Export as XML-File

You can comment on this entry
